Guide to the C-SPAN records, 1809, 1978-2012
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
C-SPAN records
1978-2012
1809-2012
C0270
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
200.0 linear feet (471 boxes)
The C-SPAN records consist of materials created and collected by the C-SPAN Corporation and its founder Brian Lamb from the years 1809, 1978-2012. The materials created by C-SPAN originate from 1978-2012, with one antique newspaper from 1809 gifted to Lamb. The records document C-SPAN's functions as a broadcasting network, as well as its continuing engagement in the political and public affairs sphere of the United States.
C-SPAN Corporation
Lamb, Brian
Long, Lea Anne
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Technical Requirements
Special Collections Research Center does not have the equipment necessary to watch Betacam or U-matic tapes, as well as other obsolete audiovisual formats contained in Series 10. Additional time and money may be required to digitize this material for access.
Acquisition Information
Donated by the C-SPAN Corporation in 2011.
Historical Information
C-SPAN (Cable-Satellite Public Affairs Network), created by the American Cable Television Industry, was founded in 1979 by Brian Lamb with the aim of televising sessions of the U.S. Congress, and offering broader access and coverage of public affairs events. C-SPAN's exact mission statements are as follows: "To provide C-SPAN's audience access to the live gavel-to-gavel proceedings of the U.S. House of Representatives and the U.S. Senate, and to other forums where public policy is discussed, debated and decided-all without editing, commentary or analysis and with a balanced presentation of points of view; To provide elected and appointed officials and others who would influence public policy a direct conduit to the audience without filtering or otherwise distorting their points of view; To provide the audience, through the call-in program, direct access to elected officials, other decision makers and journalists on a frequent and open basis; To employ production values that accurately convey the business of government rather than distract from it; and To conduct all other aspects of its operations consistent with these principles."
With an original concentration on congressional sessions, C-SPAN quickly expanded into a 24-hour network by 1982, and added call-in programs and other, non-congressional public affairs/events to its schedule. In 1986, the network expanded even more, developing the C-SPAN2 channel, which covered gavel-to-gavel Senate debates. By 2001, C-SPAN3 had launched in order to maintain full coverage of congressional sessions, as well as other original C-SPAN programming such as American History TV, The Communicators, Newsmakers, and Washington Journal. In addition to covering the U.S. Congress, C-SPAN has also covered the Executive branch of the U.S. government, including daily briefings from the White House, as well as events such as the Democratic and Republican National Conventions, and Presidential debates. One of C-SPAN's most successful endeavors was the creation of the C-SPAN Bus in 1993, which serves as a mobile production studio and learning center that visits hundreds of communities per year. The Bus, which is still being utilized, aims to engage with students, teachers, viewers, and elected officials and teach them about C-SPAN's operations. The Bus has enabled many successful educational endeavors for the network, including the Alexis de Tocqueville tour, which began in May 1997. The same year, C-SPAN expanded further with the addition of C-SPAN Radio, available in the Washington DC Metro area and nationally on satellite radio. Despite repeated efforts to do so over the past two decades, C-SPAN does not cover the U.S. Supreme Court in live TV or radio broadcast formats. C-SPAN and its sister channels enjoy strong ratings. Around the late 1980s through the early 1990s, die-hard C-SPAN watchers became known as "C-SPAN Junkies" for their dedicated viewing of and interaction with the C-SPAN network. C-SPAN maintains a consistent and large viewer base. In 2017 alone, over 70 million viewers from a wide range of backgrounds and political persuasions have accessed C-SPAN across their various platforms.
C-SPAN's founder, Brian Lamb, was an integral part of the development of the network. Lamb was a White House telecommunications policy staffer and Washington bureau chief for Cablevision magazine prior to creating C-SPAN, and brought valuable experience and insight to the job. Lamb is renowned for his many interviews and interviewing style, which was evident from the early days of the C-SPAN daily call in. Lamb's interviewing style was highlighted on his show "Booknotes" (1989-2004) where he interviewed 801 authors of mostly non-fiction books, making the show the longest-running author interview program in broadcast history. The success of "Booknotes" led to the creation of "Book TV" in 1998, a 48-hour weekend programming block dedicated to covering nonfiction books. After thirty-three years of service to the network, Lamb retired as CEO of C-SPAN in 2012, but remains its executive chairman. Lamb was succeeded by Susan Swain and Rob Kennedy as co-CEOs. Lamb's longtime secretary Lea Anne Long also contributed to C-SPAN's functions, planning events and his complicated and numerous travel itineraries. Lamb currently hosts the show "Q and A" on C-SPAN, which "highlights today's most compelling thinkers in politics, media, education, and science," and has been running since 2004. Lamb's strong and singular legacy on C-SPAN continues to this day. Lamb was awarded the National Humanities Medal in 2002 and the Presidential Medal of Freedom in 2007 for his extensive work in broadcasting over the years.
Scope and Content
The C-SPAN records largely consist of correspondence, viewer mail, photographs, photographic negatives, slides, newspapers, audiovisual materials, posters, pamphlets, memorabilia, and books created between the years 1978-2012. The collection contains 12 series.
Series 1: Press Clippings (1978-2012) includes press clippings related to C-SPAN and Brian Lamb from a wide variety of sources, including the Washington Post, New York Times, Newsweek, USA Today, Los Angeles Times, and multiple local-level newspapers. Topics range from international politics to the public perception of C-SPAN, as well as events such as C-SPAN's 25th Anniversary, programming, and political news.
Series 2: Routers (1984-1996) includes multiple press clips from a variety of sources and newspapers that were routed to Lamb and C-SPAN staff, covering topics such as presidential campaigns, the Lincoln-Douglas Debates, and the C-SPAN Bus, 1994-1995 tour.
Series 3: C-SPAN Bus Clippings (1993-1994) includes multiple press clip routers on the C-SPAN Bus from a variety of sources and newspapers for both Lamb and C-SPAN staff. The Bus's itinerary is also included.
Series 4: Press Releases (1985-2002) includes press releases by and about C-SPAN's activities and endeavors, which include conferences, coverage of events, new television stations broadcasting C-SPAN, speeches, and promotions. Topics also include programming, such as "Booknotes" and "Road to the White House."
Series 5: Green Room Faxes (1994) includes faxes from C-SPAN viewers that were sent to the C-SPAN studio green room. These range from positive and negative responses to coverage and programming, as well as questions directed at Brian Lamb.
Series 6: Viewer Mail (1994-2004) includes viewer mail responding to multiple events and topics shown on C-SPAN. Includes responses to C-SPAN programming, coverage, current events, politics, and responses directed to Brian Lamb. Formats range widely, from handwritten to typed letters and greeting cards, to notecards and postcards, and other printed materials.
Series 7: Education and Marketing (1989-2009) includes materials related to C-SPAN's various education and marketing campaigns. Topics include Viewer of the Week, American Writers, Campaign 2000 Educator's Conference, Alexis de Tocqueville, Lincoln-Douglas Series, and the C-SPAN School Bus. Other notable materials include original mixed-media portraits of famous authors and program transcripts of C-SPAN programming.
Series 8: Executive Files and Correspondence (1976-2009) includes the majority of Lamb's personal correspondence with a number of individuals and organizations. Also includes documents related to C-SPAN's operating budget, Board Meetings and Executive Committee Meetings memoranda, press clippings, "Booknotes" materials and manuscripts, tour speeches, C-SPAN 2000, 20th Anniversary planning materials, and Time Warner Cable v. The City of New York court documents.
Series 9: Photographs (1978-2008) includes photographs, photographic negatives, and slides of a variety of C-SPAN's functions, including coverage of the Democratic and Republican National Conventions and other public events, individuals who worked for and with C-SPAN, and Brian Lamb's activities and events he attended during that time.
Series 10: Audiovisual (1980s-2012) includes a wide variey of analog audiovisual formats and content, ranging from interviews with C-SPAN's board members, press clips, and public events, to graphic design mock ups and digital photographs. Formats include VHS tapes, U-matic tapes, floppy disks, cassette tapes, CDs, and DVDs, among others.
Series 11: Memorabilia (1980s-2012) includes memorabilia gathered from multiple C-SPAN functions and programs, such as the Tocqueville Tour, the Lincoln-Douglas Debates reenactment, the C-SPAN Bus, coverage of Presidential elections, in a variety of formats such as pens, pencils, pins, stickers, keychains, and many more.
Series 12: Miscellaneous (1809-2012) includes miscellaneous items such as award plaques gifted to C-SPAN and Brian Lamb from a number of organizations, newspapers, C-SPAN advertisements, loose scrapbook pages, exhibit panels of varying sizes, C-SPAN political cartoons, and an antique newspaper from 1809 given to Brian Lamb.
Bibliography
Arrangement
Series 1: Press Clippings, 1978-2012 (Boxes 1-51)
Series 2: Routers, 1984-1996 (Boxes 51-60)
Series 3: C-SPAN Bus Clippings, 1993-1994 (Boxes 60-61)
Series 4: Press Releases, 1985-2002 (Boxes 61-75)
Series 5: Green Room Faxes, 1994 (Boxes 75-91)
Series 6: Viewer Mail, 1994-2004 (Boxes 91-145)
Series 7: Education and Marketing, 1989-2009 (Boxes 145-229)
Series 8: Executive Files and Correspondence, 1976-2009 (Boxes 229-402)
Series 9: Photographs, 1978-2008 (Boxes 403-444)
Series 10: Audiovisual, 1980s-2012 (Boxes 445-452)
Series 11: Memorabilia, 1980s-2012 (Boxes 453-456)
Series 12: Miscellaneous, 1809-2012 (Boxes 457-470, Map Cases 5.2 - 5.5)
Related Material
George Mason University also houses the Booknotes collection, which contains 801 nonfiction books used on the "Booknotes" television series, hosted by Brian Lamb. Scanned images of Brian Lamb's own "book notes" are available online. More information is available on the. Purdue University houses the C-SPAN Video Library. More information is available on the.
Index Terms
Persons:
Lamb, Brian; Long, Lea Anne; Tocqueville, Alexis de
Geographical Names:
United States--Politics and government.; Washington (D.C.)
Subjects:
Advertisements; Broadcast journalism; Broadcasting; C-SPAN (Television network); Cable television; Direct broadcast satellite television; Education, Elementary; Educators; Journalism--United States.; Lincoln-Douglas Debates, Ill., 1858; Political campaigns--United States.; Politics; Presidents--Elections; Presidents--United States.; Press; Public affairs television programs; Television; Television and children; Television programs--United States.; Television viewers; Television viewers--United States; Television--United States.; United States. Congress; United States. Congress. House; United States. Congress. Senate
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Memorabilia.; Negatives.; Newspapers.; Photographs.; Slides.; Sound recordings.; Video recordings.
Contents List
- Series 1: Press Clippings (Boxes 1-51), 1978-2012
  Includes press clippings related to C-SPAN and Brian Lamb from a wide variety of sources, including the Washington Post, New York Times, Newsweek, USA Today, Los Angeles Times, and multiple local-level newspapers. Topics range from international politics to the public perception of C-SPAN, as well as events such as C-SPAN's 25th Anniversary, programming, and political news.
  - Various, 1978-1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Media Clips, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1979 Media (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Media Clips, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Broadcasting, Various Stories, 1979-1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Media Clips, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Media Clips, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Media Clips, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Press Clippings, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Media Clips (Various), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Media Clips (Various), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Washington Post Articles, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - USA Today, Assorted Articles, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Magazine Articles, Award Nomination, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - CableVision "On the Road with C-SPAN's Brian Lamb,", 1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "Cam Scam" Editorials, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - General Coverage for Board Members, April 18, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Media Institute Brian Lamb Speech, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - National Organization on Disability, Fall 1984 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - New York Times, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Other Newspapers, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Roll Call, March 22, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - USA Today, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Various Sources, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Various Sources, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Various Sources "Camscam,", 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Various Sources, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Various Sources, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Various Sources, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Various (Trade Magazine) Sources, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Various Election Coverage Mentions, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Various Sources, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Various Sources, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Various Sources, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Various Sources, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cable Marketing, "C-SPAN Plans Alternative Coverage of 1984 Election,", January 1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - SAT Guide, "Bringing Home the House,", January 1984 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Various Sources, Election '84 Coverage, January-March, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Various Sources, January 1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - New York Times, "C-SPAN on the Move,", January 1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Electronic Media, "Senate should quit hiding,", January 1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Multichannel News, "C-SPAN and CNN Gear up to Cover 1984 Campaigns,", January 16, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Cablevision Plus, Election Coverage, January 16, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Associated Press, Convention Coverage, January 17, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Various Sources, State of the Union, January 25, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - New York Times, "Gearing up for Electin Year," Stevel Knoll, January 29, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Multichannel News, "Washington Social Event Loses in Translation to TV via C-SPAN,", January 30, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Washington Post, House Cable System, January 30, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Gannett News Service, Various Articles, February 1984 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - On Cable, "Making TV History Day by Day,", February 1984 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Various Sources in New Hampshire, Primary Campaign, February 1984 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Des Moines Register, Iowa Primary Race Coverage, February 1984 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - USA Today, "O'Neill fires shot in House TV war,", February 1984 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Washington Times, "Millions see politics first-hand cable TV,", February 2, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Electronic Media, "Videos hit big on Capitol Hill,", February 2, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Multichannel News, "Iowa Caucus Coverage Kicks Off Cable's 1984 Campaign Coverage,", February 6, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Village Voice, "Back to the Booth to You-ZAP!,", February 7, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - New York Times, "A Channel That Focuses on Government,", February 8, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Congressional Quarterly, "Televised Partisan Skurmishes Erupt in House,", February 11, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Associated Press, "C-SPAN," Bill McCloskey, February 13, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Editor and Publisher, "Cable for Cartoonist,", February 13, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - United Press International, "C-SPAN,", February 14, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - USA Today, "How TV trails candidates to the election,", February 17, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Cableday Magazine, "Cable syas 'call-in!',", February 18, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Des Moines Register, "Cable TV's unedited coverage of events leading to caucuses,", February 18, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Boston Globe, "Conservatives use House TV to advantage,", February 19, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Washington Post "When will they stop covering the Conventions?,", February 20, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Multichannel News, February 20, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Philadelphia Inquirer, "1984 racer rate full coverage on C-SPAN,", February 21,1984 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - St. Louis Post Dispatch, "C-SPAN: Unique Coverage,", February 22, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Montgomery Journal, "24-hour TV politics given eye on power," GMU server as C-SPAN's local 'Capitol Connection,'" "Area students combine politics with TV,", February 24, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - New Hampshire Sunday News, "Watching Them Watch Us,", February 26, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Tom Shales "If election were held today,", February 27, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Multichannel News, "C-SPAN's Iowa Caucus Coverage offers Insight without Hoopla," and "Cable news off to Fast Start with coverage of Iowa Caucus,", February 27, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Various Sources, Florida Primary Coverage, March 1984 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Des Moines Register "Showing it as it really is,", March 1, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Milwaukee Sentinel, "Chief calls C-SPAN 'video verite',", March 1, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Broadcasting, "The week the media moved on New Hampshire,", March 5, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Multichannel News, "N.Y. Gov Seeks to Launch State Version of C-SPAN,", March 5, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Cable Vision, "C-SPAN Caucus Coverage,", March 5, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Forbes, "TV or not TV?,", March 12, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Channel Guide, "Nets Scramble to Cover Election,", March 18, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - UPI wires on "Tip" and Anniversary, March 19, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - USA Today, "O'Neill fire shot in House TV war,", March 19, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Multichannel News, "C-SPAN Begins Drive for Financial Backers,", March 19, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Cable Vision, "C-SPAN kicks off Fund Drive,", March 19, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Chicago Tribune, "Cable's no-frills public affairs network seeks coverage by corporate funder,", March 19, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Albany Times-Union, Brian Lamb letter to the Editor, March 19, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Congressional Record, 'Congratulations to C-SPAN on its fifth anniversary,", March 19, 21, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Philadelphia Inquirer, "C-SPAN celebrates 5th year of innovative information,", March 20, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - USA Today, "C-SPAN is raising funds for new coverage,", March 21 1984 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Electronic Media, "House Celebrate five years on air,", March 22, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Roll Call, "C-SPAN grew with House coverage,", March 22, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Los Angeles Times "TheThinking Man's Channel,", March 22, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Broadcasting, Editorials, March 26, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Cable Vision, "Promise Fulfilled,", March 26, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - SJR "GOP 'young turks pay to the gallery', April 1984 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Electronic Media, "C-SPAN Plans own Democratic Convention feed,", April 5, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - National Journal, "Strides in Technology are Changing,", April 7, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - New York Times "C-SPAN Strives to Expand,", April 8, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Multichannel News, "Canadian Ops Given OK to Carry 17 U.S. Services,", April 9, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Cablevision, "C-SPAN Heightens Awareness,", April 9, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Wall Street Journal, "A Fix for Political Junkies,", April 15, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Multichannel News, "C-SPAN to use own cameras at Democratic Convention,", April 16, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Cable Vision, "C-SPAN to uplink NCTA Las Vegas Convention,", April 16, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - New York Times, "A House Divided: Those Candid TV Cameras,", April 18, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Washington Post "Congress: Best Little Soap Opera on Cable,", April 29, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Associated Press, "Republicans Testing Tip O'Neill as TV Target,", May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Cox News Service, "C-SPAN Praised as great teacher," Bob Dart, May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - James McGregor, "Vin Weber, 2 other conservatives rile Dems with House TV 'shows',", May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Carl Rowan, "Shams that impression our Congress,", May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Gannett News Service, "Congressman turns star on C-SPAN,", May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Richard Viguerie, "Uncle Tom's Camera,", May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Cox News Service, "Tip O'Neill versus the wired society," Jim Fain, May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Associated Press, "TV issues sparks shouting match,", May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Copley News Service, "Percy, Dixon favor TV in Senate Despite the 'CamScam' donnybrook," Robert Estill, May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Associated Press, " 'Don't Touch That Dial...'" Tom Raum, May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Associated Press, 'GOP TV ads depict O'Neill as a tyrant; Dems cry 'foul',", May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Gannett News Service, "Tip produces good TV show," Dick Dougherty, May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Chicago Tribune, "House kicks off silly season with TV ruckus," Raymond Coffey, May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - United Press International, "Democrats let TV scan House and GOP cries 'cheap trick',", May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Newspaper Enterprise Association, "House's 'Funny' Fued Is No Joke," Robert Wagman, May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Knight-Ridder, "House heats up; O'Neill speech rules out of roder,", May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - "Camscam" Clip compilation #2, May-June 1984 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Tom Shales, "We're lucky to have television to cover the great television issues of our day,", May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Otis Pike, "A riles speaker changes the rules,", May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Scott Shepard, "House Speaker assails Gingrich for criticizing Nicaragua letter,", May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Cable Marketing, "Marketing to play key Role in C-SPAN Awareness Drive,", May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Various Sources, "Camscam,", May-June 1984 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Various Sources, Editorial Cartoons, May-June 1984 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Congressional Record, May 10,1984 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Various Sources, House Democrats and TV, May 10, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Washington Post "Panning of an Empty Chamber by TV Cameras," T.R. Reid, May 12, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - San Juan Star, "GOP Protests Change,", May 12, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Associated Press, "Revealing TV camera helps House Speaker avenge his opponents,", May 13, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Broadcasting, "C-SPAN outtakes still at issue,", May 14, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 77)